<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<calendar>
    <mise_en_forme_par>
        <unCreateur>Moi</unCreateur>
        <unCreateur>Mon binome</unCreateur>
        <NoBinome>B3100</NoBinome>
    </mise_en_forme_par>
    <date>01/05/2014</date>
    <type>TV Shows</type>
    <version>2.0</version>
    <timezone>Europe/Paris</timezone>
    <event uid="22923141397120400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140410T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140410T024500</dtend>
        <description>After the shocking death of one of their own, Clarke and Finn grow closer as they try to figure out a way to communicate with the Ark. Bellamy must keep the group from turning on one another as life on Earth takes a desperate turn. Meanwhile, Abby risks having herself floated in order to give Raven the chance to stow-away in the escape pod bound for Earth.</description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x04 "Murphy's Law"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="66684121397124000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140410T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140410T033000</dtend>
        <description>The guys confront an online gamer who's been terrorizing them.</description>
        <title>Workaholics</title>
        <summary>Workaholics 4x12 "DeputyDong"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/workaholics/season/4/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="55121397203200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140411T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140411T013000</dtend>
        <description>Subway makes plans to turn Greendale into Subway University; Jeff considers an employment offer; Dean Pelton tells Annie and Abed about the school's first dean.</description>
        <title>Community</title>
        <summary>Community 5x12 "Basic Story"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/community/season/5/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="347201397203200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140411T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140411T013000</dtend>
        <description>Sheldon has a personal crisis when he decides string theory is a waste of his time; a double date ends in embarrassment for Howard.</description>
        <title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
        <summary>The Big Bang Theory 7x20 "The Relationship Diremption"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-big-bang-theory/season/7/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="226191397205000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140411T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140411T015000</dtend>
        <description>In the midst of flu season, a sick Leslie and Andy struggle to book performers for the Unity Concert. Meanwhile, Tom heads to a wine competition in search of a sommelier for his new restaurant, and Ben seeks drunken help from Ron with a personal problem.</description>
        <title>Parks and Recreation</title>
        <summary>Parks and Recreation 6x19 "Flu Season 2"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/parks-and-recreation/season/6/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9310191397206800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140411T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140411T030000</dtend>
        <description>Cristina is nominated for a Harper Avery and although most of her fellow doctors are ecstatic, she won’t let herself get too excited. Bailey continues to work on a young boy without an immune system -- Alex considers making a change, and Derek and Callie work with a machine that can recognize emotions. Meanwhile, Richard gives the residents a pep talk about the exciting projects going on around the hospital.</description>
        <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
        <summary>Grey's Anatomy 10x19 "I'm Winning"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/greys-anatomy/season/10/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="96173161397206800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140411T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140411T024500</dtend>
        <description>Things are anything but business as usual when Harvey and Mike find themselves at odds with a tenacious U.S. Attorney. Scottie and Harvey can’t seem to get on the same page and Mike and Rachel clash over plans for the future.</description>
        <title>Suits</title>
        <summary>Suits 3x16 "No Way Out"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suits/season/3/episode/16</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="164692201397210400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140411T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140411T040000</dtend>
        <description>A pickpocket dies of anthrax poisoning, putting Holmes and Watson on the trail of the toxin’s source in order to prevent more deaths.</description>
        <title>Elementary</title>
        <summary>Elementary 2x20 "No Lack of Void"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/elementary/season/2/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="11578291397289600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140412T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140412T020000</dtend>
        <description>Carrie catches a deadly assassin who has eluded her before, but must put her personal vendetta aside when it’s revealed that the woman has vital information to prevent a terrorist attack on New York City.</description>
        <title>Unforgettable</title>
        <summary>Unforgettable 2x09 "Flesh and Blood"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/unforgettable/season/2/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="99383181397293200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140412T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140412T024500</dtend>
        <description>Nick and his mom, Kelly Burkhardt, join forces to protect Adalind's baby. Meanwhile, Prince Viktor activates a deadly stateside asset to find Adalind and her child.</description>
        <title>Grimm</title>
        <summary>Grimm 3x18 "The Law of Sacrifice"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/grimm/season/3/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="844191397293200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140412T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140412T030000</dtend>
        <description>Five-0 is set up when a bad tip leads them to an abandoned building that is rigged to explode with McGarrett and Danny trapped inside.</description>
        <title>Hawaii Five-0</title>
        <summary>Hawaii Five-0 4x19 "Ku I Ka Pili Koko"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hawaii-five0/season/4/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="16689271397296800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140412T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140412T034500</dtend>
        <description>When Jack Crawford’s star pupil Miriam Lass is found alive, she becomes the FBI’s best hope to identifying the Chesapeake Ripper, but her foggy memory complicates the search. Evidence found at the site of Miriam’s rescue exonerates Will Graham of any involvement in the Ripper and Copycat cases, and he is released from the asylum. Will warns Dr. Chilton that he could be in danger due to his intimate knowledge of the Ripper case, but when Chilton tries to confide in Jack that he shares Will’s fears about Hannibal, he is rebuffed — no evidence has been found against Hannibal, despite the FBI’s efforts. Meanwhile, Jack wastes no time in reinstating Will on the BAU team as they hunt for the Ripper. After introducing Will and Miriam to compare notes, Jack’s suspicions of Hannibal’s involvement continue to build. Only Miriam’s memory holds the key to unlocking the Ripper’s true identity, but can it be trusted?</description>
        <title>Hannibal</title>
        <summary>Hannibal 2x07 "Yakimono"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hannibal/season/2/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="73510161397460600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T003000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T010000</dtend>
        <description>Afraid that Hayley lacks life skills, Stan makes her take a job as a bartender; when Bullock (Patrick Stewart) becomes Hayley's best customer, Stan uses his daughter's knowledge to get ahead at work.</description>
        <title>American Dad!</title>
        <summary>American Dad! 10x16 "She Swill Survive"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/american-dad/season/10/episode/16</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="106463171397462400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T020000</dtend>
        <description>Ariel returns to Storybrooke and pleads with Hook to help her find Prince Eric, who never returned to the town when the new curse was invoked. Emma agrees to let Regina teach her how to use magic so that she can help defeat Zelena, and Mary Margaret and David try to prove that they can be just as much fun as Hook is with Henry -- who thinks they are boring. Meanwhile, in Fairy Tale Land during the past year, an angry Ariel confronts Hook over her missing Prince Eric, who she assumes was kidnapped and possibly killed by the swarthy pirate. But when Hook confesses that the Jolly Roger has been stolen and Eric is most likely the thief’s prisoner, Ariel unknowingly provides him with a clue as to who the culprit is, and Hook – with Ariel in tow - goes off in search of his ship.</description>
        <title>Once Upon a Time</title>
        <summary>Once Upon a Time (2011) 3x17 "The Jolly Roger"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/once-upon-a-time-2011/season/3/episode/17</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6525181397462400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T012500</dtend>
        <description>Set in the future, Homer has a new clone for every time he dies. Lisa is married to a zombie version of Milhouse, while Bart deals with custody issues with his ex-wife, Jenda. Each defines what love means to them.</description>
        <title>The Simpsons</title>
        <summary>The Simpsons 25x18 "Days of Future Future"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-simpsons/season/25/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23908161397466000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T030000</dtend>
        <description>The Ship of the Imagination ventures on an epic voyage to the bottom of a dewdrop to explore the universe on the smallest scale and observe exotic life forms invisible to the naked eye. Then, host Neil deGrasse Tyson explains the neural network in our brains which determine our sense of smell and memory, and later, he travels deep beneath the surface of the Earth to discover the most mysterious particle we know.</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x06 "Deeper, Deeper, Deeper Still"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="334651397466000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T030000</dtend>
        <description>Jane represents a bullied pro cheerleader; Teri pretends to be Paul's lawyer when he gets in trouble for accumulating too much credit card debt; Grayson and Owen defend a family who installed speed bumps on their busy neighborhood street; Jane and Grayson make plans for a romantic evening.</description>
        <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
        <summary>Drop Dead Diva 6x05 "Cheers and Jeers"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/drop-dead-diva/season/6/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395421397466000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T030000</dtend>
        <description>A who’s who of honored guests turns out for Joffrey and Margaery’s wedding in King’s Landing, but the king’s taste in entertainment rubs many of them the wrong way. Meanwhile, Bronn gives a lesson to an unlikely pupil; Bran’s vision helps map out his journey; Stannis loses patience with Davos; and Ramsay takes a perverse delight in his new pet.</description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x02 "The Lion and the Rose"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="3385171397466000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T030000</dtend>
        <description>Alicia and Diane consider merging their firms in the wake of Will's death, even as they find themselves on opposite sides of a contentious divorce suit. Meanwhile, Alicia offers assistance to Finn when it becomes clear that the State's Attorney is looking for a scapegoat in the Jeffrey Grant case.</description>
        <title>The Good Wife</title>
        <summary>The Good Wife 5x17 "A Material World"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-good-wife/season/5/episode/17</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="20711397469600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T040000</dtend>
        <description>Don makes a new friend. Joan meets a client for drinks. Peggy hears impressive new work. Roger has a puzzling phone call.</description>
        <title>Mad Men</title>
        <summary>Mad Men 7x01 "Time Zones"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/mad-men/season/7/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23332121397469600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T033000</dtend>
        <description>After a celebratory party at the Hacker Hostel, Richard and Erlich learn that Peter Gregory won't pay up until they deliver a viable business plan that includes a slimmed-downed staff. A desperate Richard hires former Belson underling Jared, and they set about trying to trim the fat. While Gilfoyle and Dinesh prove essential, Big Head's place in the company is less certain.</description>
        <title>Silicon Valley</title>
        <summary>Silicon Valley 1x02 "The Cap Table"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/silicon-valley/season/1/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="57996171397469600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140414T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140414T040000</dtend>
        <description>Jane and the FBI take up the cause of a death row inmate who has two days to prove his innocence before his sentence is carried out.</description>
        <title>The Mentalist</title>
        <summary>The Mentalist 6x17 "Silver Wings of Time"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-mentalist/season/6/episode/17</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="929211397548800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140415T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140415T020000</dtend>
        <description>The Jeffersonian team investigates the murder of a woman whose remains were found in a swamp. When the team realizes that her body was cryogenically frozen before it was disposed, it leads them to a cryogenic preservation facility where they learn more about the victim's personal life. Meanwhile, Cam is hesitant to meet Arastoo's father and mother for the first time and Booth is up for a huge promotion that could uproot his entire family.</description>
        <title>Bones</title>
        <summary>Bones 9x21 "The Cold in the Case"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bones/season/9/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23307191397548800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140415T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140415T020000</dtend>
        <description>Roman argues with Emery about whether he can trust his uncle Castor. However, when Roman asks his uncle about the day their spaceship crashed, Castor’s reaction is far from what he expected. Meanwhile, Grayson tries to remember what happened the night he blacked out, and Taylor throws a “meteor shower” party to spend more time with Drake. Still unable to deny her feelings for Roman, Teri makes a decision that puts her in grave danger.</description>
        <title>Star-Crossed</title>
        <summary>Star-Crossed 1x09 "Some Consequence Yet Hanging in the Stars"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/starcrossed/season/1/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="27511397552400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140415T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140415T024500</dtend>
        <description>When Paracelsus takes control of Warehouse 13, it proves to only be the first step in his plan to recreate the entire world in his image. To stop him, Pete and Myka must follow him back through time to 1541 and prevent him from killing the Regents and becoming the permanent master of the Warehouses.</description>
        <title>Warehouse 13</title>
        <summary>Warehouse 13 5x01 "Endless Terror"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/warehouse-13/season/5/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1145161397635200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140416T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140416T020000</dtend>
        <description>Blaine suffers a crisis of confidence after gaining the dreaded “Freshman Fifteen.” Artie discovers that his newfound success with the ladies comes at a price. Mercedes tells Sam she’s still a virgin.</description>
        <title>Glee</title>
        <summary>Glee 5x16 "Tested"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/glee/season/5/episode/16</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="191851181397635200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140416T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140416T020000</dtend>
        <description>[watched/collected]\n\nWith Colonel Glenn Talbot now on their trail, Coulson and his team seek refuge in the last place anyone would look, where they begin to uncover S.H.I.E.L.D.'s most dangerous secrets--secrets that could destroy them all.</description>
        <title>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
        <summary>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. 1x18 "Providence"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/marvels-agents-of-shield/season/1/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6811211397635200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140416T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140416T014500</dtend>
        <description>After a Navy officer is found dead on a rural road, the NCIS team must ascertain if the murder was the result of a bar fight or because he knew too much about an attack on a fellow female officer. Meanwhile, DiNozzo and McGee start a juice cleanse to purge their bodies of impurities.</description>
        <title>NCIS</title>
        <summary>NCIS 11x21 "Alleged"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis/season/11/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1165211397638800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140416T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140416T024500</dtend>
        <description>When an undercover NCIS agent is suspected of working for the smuggler he’s supposed to be investigating, the team takes him into custody to find his true intentions. Meanwhile, Kensi and Deeks discuss their personal relationship as Kensi returns to the field.</description>
        <title>NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
        <summary>NCIS: Los Angeles 5x21 "Three Hearts"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis-los-angeles/season/5/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="96353211397638800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140416T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140416T023000</dtend>
        <description>The morning after their break-up, Jess and Nick scramble to keep it a secret from the loftmates. Meanwhile, Winston passes his police academy entrance exam, and demands that the gang throw him a "Honey Roast."</description>
        <title>New Girl</title>
        <summary>New Girl 3x21 "Big News"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/new-girl/season/3/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879111397642400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140416T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140416T040000</dtend>
        <description>A ruthless, manipulative man meets a small town insurance salesman and sets him on a path of destruction.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x01 "The Crocodile's Dilemma"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113673201397642400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140416T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140416T040000</dtend>
        <description>Reese goes under cover as a secret service agent in order to get close to the latest person of interest, a congressman who may have the key to derailing Decima's plan for a second machine.</description>
        <title>Person of Interest</title>
        <summary>Person of Interest 3x20 "Death Benefit"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/person-of-interest/season/3/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="163272191397721600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140417T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140417T014500</dtend>
        <description>Oliver, Canary, Diggle and Felicity return to the lair and find Slade waiting for them. An epic battle breaks out and one member of Team Arrow is sent to the hospital. Thea hits her breaking point, but just as Oliver is about to reach her, Slade intervenes and Oliver is faced with a choice – his battle with Slade or his family. Meanwhile, Laurel struggles with a new secret.</description>
        <title>Arrow</title>
        <summary>Arrow 2x19 "The Man Under the Hood"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/arrow/season/2/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="22923151397725200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140417T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140417T024500</dtend>
        <description>Clarke’s newfound romance with Finn is threatened. Octavia suffers a blow to the head and wakes up to find a Grounder watching her. On the Ark, Abby exposes Kane’s plan to reduce the population of the Ark. Jaha and Abby notice a signal and realize at least some of the 100 must still be alive on Earth.</description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x05 "Twilight's Last Gleaming"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="66684131397728800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140417T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140417T033000</dtend>
        <description>The guys celebrate their common law marriage.</description>
        <title>Workaholics</title>
        <summary>Workaholics 4x13 "Friendship Anniversary"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/workaholics/season/4/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="55131397808000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140418T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140418T013000</dtend>
        <description>When everyone learns about Greendale's first dean, they embark on a mission to find his old computer lab; Subway enlists Chang to spy on the group as part of its plan to take over the school.</description>
        <title>Community</title>
        <summary>Community 5x13 "Basic Sandwich"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/community/season/5/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="226201397809800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140418T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140418T015000</dtend>
        <description>Leslie and Ben run a charity auction to raise funds for the unity concert. April steps in to manage Andy's schedule, while Donna asks Ron for help with her ex-boyfriend.</description>
        <title>Parks and Recreation</title>
        <summary>Parks and Recreation 6x20 "One in 8,000"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/parks-and-recreation/season/6/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9310201397811600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140418T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140418T030000</dtend>
        <description>Cristina enlists Meredith to help her prepare an acceptance speech for her possible Harper Avery win and while Owen offers to attend the ceremony with her, she insists on going alone. Meanwhile, Derek feels overwhelmed between his responsibilities at home and at the hospital. April and Jackson come to a disagreement on children and religion, and Callie and Arizona try to reconnect in their marriage.</description>
        <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
        <summary>Grey's Anatomy 10x20 "Go It Alone"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/greys-anatomy/season/10/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="115782101397894400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140419T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140419T020000</dtend>
        <description>The murder of a prominent lawyer leads Carrie and Al to reexamine a rape case that moved Manhattan thirteen years before. Soon, they realize that the case was not as clear cut as it was portrayed by the media, and an innocent man may have been wrongfully convicted.</description>
        <title>Unforgettable</title>
        <summary>Unforgettable 2x10 "Manhunt"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/unforgettable/season/2/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="16689281397901600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140419T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140419T034500</dtend>
        <description>When a young woman's body is discovered inside of a horse, Hannibal suggests to Jack that Will be brought in to help crack this peculiar case. Will has seemingly cast aside his suspicions of Hannibal, resuming their doctor-patient relationship, but Alana remains skeptical regarding Will's true intentions and worries that Hannibal may still be in danger. The FBI questions the man they suspect to be the killer in their case, but lack of evidence forces them to let him go. Will and Hannibal race to guard the safety of a witness they believe is in jeopardy, but it might be Will's own judgment that is in peril.</description>
        <title>Hannibal</title>
        <summary>Hannibal 2x08 "Su-zakana"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hannibal/season/2/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="106463181398067200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T020000</dtend>
        <description>After Zelena steals Regina's heart, Regina casts a spell so that she can speak across the realms to her dead mother, Cora, to discover the truth about why she abandoned Zelena, and Belle stumbles across what Zelena's ultimate end game is. Meanwhile, in the Fairy Tale Land that was, young Cora is duped by a man claiming to be a prince and finds herself alone and pregnant. But a chance meeting with a real prince could lead Cora to the royal life she's always craved, but she must keep her pregnancy a secret or risk losing everything.</description>
        <title>Once Upon a Time</title>
        <summary>Once Upon a Time (2011) 3x18 "Bleeding Through"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/once-upon-a-time-2011/season/3/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23908171398070800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T030000</dtend>
        <description>To determine the true age of the Earth, geochemist Clair Patterson developed the uranium-lead dating method to make an unprecedented discovery – calculating Earth's age of 4.5 billion years. But Patterson's groundbreaking discoveries were just beginning. Patterson made it his mission to draw public attention to the detrimental effects of lead in the environment and dedicated his career to fighting against the petroleum and chemical industry, eventually achieving public health's biggest victory of the 20th century.</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x07 "The Clean Room"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395431398070800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T030000</dtend>
        <description>In the frenzied aftermath of the royal wedding, Tyrion gets a visit from a loyal subject, but wonders if anyone in his family will help him out of his current predicament. Meanwhile, Tywin offers to work for the common good with a presumed enemy. Sam takes stock of the personnel at Castle Black. The Hound gives another life lesson to Arya, and Daenerys makes a decision outside the walls of Meereen.</description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x03 "Breaker of Chains"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="3385181398070800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T030000</dtend>
        <description>Florrick/Agos takes on the case of an NSA whistleblower, only to learn that the agency has been monitoring the firm as well as Alicia’s personal life. Meanwhile, Diane faces the difficult task of working alongside Louis Canning when he joins Lockhart/Gardner. Also, Alicia goes after the State’s Attorney when he attempts to make Finn a scapegoat in the Jeffrey Grant case.</description>
        <title>The Good Wife</title>
        <summary>The Good Wife 5x18 "All Tapped Out"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-good-wife/season/5/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028211398074400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T040000</dtend>
        <description>Marisol finds a new love; Peri goes to great lengths to keep Spence and Rosie apart; Zoila discovers that Valentina is back from Africa; Carmen and Alejandro settle in to their fake relationship; Odessa reaches her limit; Adrian and Evelyn hire a handsome bodyguard.</description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x01 "An Ideal Husband"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="20721398074400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T040000</dtend>
        <description>Peggy receives a bouquet of flowers at the office. Pete navigates the politics of new business. Joan is put in an impossibly awkward situation.</description>
        <title>Mad Men</title>
        <summary>Mad Men 7x02 "A Day's Work"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/mad-men/season/7/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23332131398074400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T033000</dtend>
        <description>While Gavin Belson begins to hype Nucleus, a competing compression platform, Richard learns that the name Pied Piper is already registered to a sprinkler company, forcing him to negotiate. Meanwhile, Erlich goes on a vision quest for a new company name, and Peter Gregory proves elusive when one of his companies asks for money.</description>
        <title>Silicon Valley</title>
        <summary>Silicon Valley 1x03 "Articles of Incorporation"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/silicon-valley/season/1/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="57996181398074400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140421T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140421T040000</dtend>
        <description>When a woman is found murdered near a remote men’s social club, Jane must find a way to insinuate himself into the insular group to find the killer.</description>
        <title>The Mentalist</title>
        <summary>The Mentalist 6x18 "Forest Green"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-mentalist/season/6/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="308611398150000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140422T000000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140422T001100</dtend>
        <description>In order to find Finn's father, Finn and Jake must commit a cosmic crime...unless the Lich beats them to it.</description>
        <title>Adventure Time</title>
        <summary>Adventure Time 6x01 "Wake Up"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/adventure-time/season/6/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="308621398150000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140422T000000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140422T001100</dtend>
        <description>Finn and Jake follow the Lich to the Citadel, where Finn meets his long lost dad. But just how far does the apple fall from the tree?</description>
        <title>Adventure Time</title>
        <summary>Adventure Time 6x02 "Escape From the Citadel"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/adventure-time/season/6/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="929221398153600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140422T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140422T020000</dtend>
        <description>The Jeffersonian team investigates the death of Stephanie McNamara, the daughter of a wealthy family whose remains were found in a national park. When the team digs deeper into the circumstances surrounding her death, clues from the case lead them to believe she may be the Ghost Killer’s latest victim, with a surprising connection to a previous victim. Meanwhile, the FBI Deputy Director takes a special interest in the team’s high-profile case and Booth’s career may be in for some changes.</description>
        <title>Bones</title>
        <summary>Bones 9x22 "The Nail in the Coffin"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bones/season/9/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="233071101398153600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140422T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140422T020000</dtend>
        <description>A hurricane suddenly hits the town and everyone is trapped inside the school. Teri drugs Roman, which leaves him very paranoid and very angry. While drugged he says some very hurtful things to Emery that alter their relationship. Taylor convinces Drake that they should go public as a couple. However, when Grayson overhears the couple talking, he blackmails Drake into breaking up with Taylor. Meanwhile, Julia turns to Emery for help after Eva threatens her.</description>
        <title>Star-Crossed</title>
        <summary>Star-Crossed 1x10 "What Storm Is This That Blows So?"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/starcrossed/season/1/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="27521398157200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140422T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140422T024500</dtend>
        <description>Myka and Pete encounter two secret service agents that force them to question their own relationship, while Artie attempts to show Claudia the truth about her sister.</description>
        <title>Warehouse 13</title>
        <summary>Warehouse 13 5x02 "Secret Services"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/warehouse-13/season/5/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="736201398160800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140422T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140422T040000</dtend>
        <description>When construction workers find the body of an infamous New York mobster who disappeared in the seventies, Beckett and Castle try to solve this three decade-old Mafia hit. Unfortunately, their only witness is a man who thinks it’s still the 1970’s, so to uncover what he knows, they must play into his delusion, and party like it’s the last days of disco.</description>
        <title>Castle</title>
        <summary>Castle (2009) 6x20 "That '70s Show"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/castle-2009/season/6/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="232881191398160800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140422T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140422T034500</dtend>
        <description>As the team tries to protect a target of the Pavlovich brothers -- specialists in abductions -- Red has a job of his own for the duo; Liz patiently pursues the truth about Tom.</description>
        <title>The Blacklist</title>
        <summary>The Blacklist 1x19 "The Pavlovich Brothers"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-blacklist/season/1/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1145171398240000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140423T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140423T020000</dtend>
        <description>Rachel makes her Broadway debut in "Funny Girl."</description>
        <title>Glee</title>
        <summary>Glee 5x17 "Opening Night"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/glee/season/5/episode/17</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="191851191398240000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140423T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140423T020000</dtend>
        <description>[watched/collected]\n\nWith their world turned upside down, Coulson races to save the life of his one true love as the mystery of "The Cellist," which began in Marvel's The Avengers, is finally revealed on Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.</description>
        <title>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
        <summary>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. 1x19 "The Only Light in the Darkness"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/marvels-agents-of-shield/season/1/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879121398247200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140423T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140423T040000</dtend>
        <description>Molly begins to suspect that Lester is involved with the murders, but her new boss points her in a different direction. Meanwhile, Malvo investigates the blackmail plot against a man known as the Supermarket King.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x02 "The Rooster Prince"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="163272201398326400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140424T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140424T014500</dtend>
        <description>The mirakuru sends Roy into an uncontrollable rage and he unleashes on the city. After Roy’s deadly fight with a police officer, Oliver realizes the mirakuru has taken over Roy completely and must figure out a way to stop him. Things get more complicated after Sara declares that Roy is too far gone and the only way to stop him is to kill him. Meanwhile, Thea believes she can breakthrough to Roy so she goes on camera at Moira’s campaign rally to lure him to Verdant. Her ploy works but after Roy attacks Thea, Team Arrow unleashes on him.</description>
        <title>Arrow</title>
        <summary>Arrow 2x20 "Seeing Red"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/arrow/season/2/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113613101398328200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140424T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140424T020000</dtend>
        <description>Tessa decides to mentor young social outcast in the Miss Chatswin pageant to make a statement; Victor goes missing while on a camping trip with George, Noah and Fred.</description>
        <title>Suburgatory</title>
        <summary>Suburgatory 3x10 "No, You Can't Sit with Us"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suburgatory/season/3/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="25201398330000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140424T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140424T023000</dtend>
        <description>[watched/collected]\n\nThe family joins Phil as he travels to Australia to fulfill his mother's wish that he see the land where he was conceived.</description>
        <title>Modern Family</title>
        <summary>Modern Family 5x20 "Australia"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/modern-family/season/5/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="22923161398330000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140424T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140424T024500</dtend>
        <description>Bellamy leads his crew into Grounder territory as they search for Octavia. Raven can't help but notice the deep connection between Finn and Clarke. Meanwhile, flashbacks reveal Bellamy's and Octavia's childhood on the Ark.</description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x06 "His Sister's Keeper"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="347211398412800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140425T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140425T013000</dtend>
        <description>Sheldon gives spontaneity a try, which causes unexpected friction for Penny, Bernadette and Amy; Raj asks Howard for help with preparation for a date with Emily.</description>
        <title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
        <summary>The Big Bang Theory 7x21 "The Anything Can Happen Recurrence"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-big-bang-theory/season/7/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="226211398414600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140425T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140425T015000</dtend>
        <description>Leslie, Ben, and Andy head to San Francisco for a National Parks Conference. Tom opens his restaurant, Ron has another run-in with his ex-wife Tammy 2, Andy lives a rock and roll fantasy, and Leslie makes a huge decision about her future.</description>
        <title>Parks and Recreation</title>
        <summary>Parks and Recreation 6x21 "Moving Up (1)"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/parks-and-recreation/season/6/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="226221398414600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140425T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140425T015000</dtend>
        <description>Leslie, Ben, and Andy head to San Francisco for a National Parks Conference. Tom opens his restaurant, Ron has another run-in with his ex-wife Tammy 2, Andy lives a rock and roll fantasy, and Leslie makes a huge decision about her future.</description>
        <title>Parks and Recreation</title>
        <summary>Parks and Recreation 6x22 "Moving Up (2)"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/parks-and-recreation/season/6/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9310211398416400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140425T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140425T030000</dtend>
        <description>Jackson is given the daunting task of delivering disappointing news to the doctors. Meanwhile, Derek's sister Amelia drops by for a surprise visit, Richard surprises Catherine in Boston and when Bailey gets frustrated by the slow pace of her research, she makes a risky decision.</description>
        <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
        <summary>Grey's Anatomy 10x21 "Change of Heart"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/greys-anatomy/season/10/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713111398418200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140425T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140425T030000</dtend>
        <description>[watched/collected]\n\nFormer trophy wife Meredith Davis seeks a return to a life of leisure and luxury by posing as a teacher at an upscale elementary school to meet the students' rich, single fathers and land one to marry. However, her plan hits a major snag and she faces exposure when her unconventional and mostly unsuitable teaching methods raise the suspicions of a fellow faculty member.</description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x01 "Pilot"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="164692211398420000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140425T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140425T040000</dtend>
        <description>When Sherlock’s brother Mycroft makes a surprise return to New York, his motivations cause discord between Sherlock and Joan. Meanwhile, a missing person case takes Sherlock and Joan inside the world of unmanned aeronautics.</description>
        <title>Elementary</title>
        <summary>Elementary 2x21 "The Man With the Twisted Lip"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/elementary/season/2/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="115782111398499200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140426T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140426T020000</dtend>
        <description>A murdered body washes ashore in the Hamptons, and Carrie and Al's boss offers them a "paid vacation" in his beautiful Southampton cottage, in order to help local law enforcement find the killer, who may or may not be related to a previous serial killer.</description>
        <title>Unforgettable</title>
        <summary>Unforgettable 2x11 "East of Islip"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/unforgettable/season/2/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="99383191398502800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140426T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140426T024500</dtend>
        <description>Nick and Hank investigate a dangerous female suspect leaving a trail of Wesen in her wake. Elsewhere, Adalind takes measures into her own hands, even if that means forging a dangerous alliance.</description>
        <title>Grimm</title>
        <summary>Grimm 3x19 "Nobody Knows the Trouble I've Seen"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/grimm/season/3/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="844201398502800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140426T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140426T030000</dtend>
        <description>The investigation of a murdered pool cleaner leads the Five-0 team to a possible terrorist cell of radicalized students plotting an attack on U.S. soil.</description>
        <title>Hawaii Five-0</title>
        <summary>Hawaii Five-0 4x20 "Pe'epe'e Kānaka"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hawaii-five0/season/4/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="16689291398506400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140426T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140426T034500</dtend>
        <description>The FBI is called in to investigate the discovery of a truck driver’s body, seemingly torn apart by two separate species of animal working in tandem, neither of which consumed their kill. After one of his therapy sessions, Will meets Hannibal’s  strange new patient, Margot Verger. Will and Margot compare notes on Hannibal and his unconventional advice. Continually encouraging his patients to revel in what they are, Hannibal aims to determine Will’s true self by sending him a test, the results of which surprise even Hannibal.</description>
        <title>Hannibal</title>
        <summary>Hannibal 2x09 "Shiizakana"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hannibal/season/2/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="73510171398670200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T003000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T010000</dtend>
        <description>Stan learns how to slyly check out other women; Roger and Klaus try to cover up a stain on a new couch.</description>
        <title>American Dad!</title>
        <summary>American Dad! 10x17 "Rubberneckers"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/american-dad/season/10/episode/17</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="106463191398672000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T020000</dtend>
        <description>Zelena threatens to kill Henry if Hook - whose lips have been cursed by the Wicked Witch -- doesn't proceed with kissing Emma, which will drain all of her magical powers away, and things begin to heat up between Regina and Robin Hood. Meanwhile, back in the Fairy Tale Land that was during the past year, Snow and Charming go in search of Glinda, The Good Witch of the South, to see if she can help them defeat Zelena, and the curse that will ultimately send the Fairy Tale characters back to Storybrooke is cast -- but from an unlikely source.</description>
        <title>Once Upon a Time</title>
        <summary>Once Upon a Time (2011) 3x19 "A Curious Thing"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/once-upon-a-time-2011/season/3/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6525191398672000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T012500</dtend>
        <description>When Bart develops powers that help Springfield couples conceive, the mafia kidnaps Homer and Bart in hopes of birthing a thoroughbred race horse.</description>
        <title>The Simpsons</title>
        <summary>The Simpsons 25x19 "What to Expect When Bart's Expecting"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-simpsons/season/25/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23908181398675600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T030000</dtend>
        <description>Discover the remarkable story of Annie Jump Cannon and Cecilia Payne, two incredible women who challenged conventional wisdom and uncovered the real-life story of the stars. Cannon led a group of female astronomers in the early 20th century to catalogue the spectral characters of stars, and two decades later, young British beauty Payne joined forces with  Cannon to analyze the data and uncover the chemical compositions of the stars. Later, travel on the Ship of the Imagination to explore the lives and deaths of stars and visit the planet of a star orbiting a globular cluster</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x08 "Sisters of the Sun"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="334661398675600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T030000</dtend>
        <description>Pregnant Stacy is concerned when someone suggests her frequent burping is a sign she's having an evil baby. Grayson and Jane are paired together on a case involving national security, but are flummoxed when they're given very little information about their mild mannered client or her charges. Kim represents a family of orphans when their adoptive parents kick them out immediately after home make over show renovations.</description>
        <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
        <summary>Drop Dead Diva 6x06 "Desperate Housewife"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/drop-dead-diva/season/6/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395441398675600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T030000</dtend>
        <description>Jon welcomes volunteers. Bran, Jojen, Meera and Hodor seek shelter. Jaime and Brienne discuss his honor. Daenerys balances justice and mercy.</description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x04 "Oathkeeper"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="3385191398675600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T030000</dtend>
        <description>When Alicia pays a visit to longtime client Colin Sweeney, she finds herself in the unwanted role of witness when a body is discovered in his home. Meanwhile, Eli steps in when an unfortunate picture of Zach threatens to become a public relations nightmare for Peter.</description>
        <title>The Good Wife</title>
        <summary>The Good Wife 5x19 "Tying the Knot"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-good-wife/season/5/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028221398679200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T040000</dtend>
        <description>Carmen feels threatened by an old flame from Alejandro’s past and goes to great lengths to insure that her career isn’t in jeopardy; Zoila helps Valentina with her job but ignores problems at home; Rosie begins a new job with a dysfunctional family; Marisol tries to make peace with Opal; Peri threatens Spence so he will stay in their marriage; Adrian copes with a home invasion but fails to protect Evelyn in a dangerous situation.</description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x02 "The Dark at the Top of the Stairs"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="20731398679200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T040000</dtend>
        <description>Don takes an impromptu trip. Betty has lunch with a friend. Harry lobbies for a cause. The partners consider a questionable asset.</description>
        <title>Mad Men</title>
        <summary>Mad Men 7x03 "Field Trip"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/mad-men/season/7/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23332141398679200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T033000</dtend>
        <description>At Peter's toga party, Richard drunkenly promises to make Erlich a board member, which he regrets the next morning. After being unassigned at Hooli, Big Head finds others like him who have made careers out of doing nothing. Richard struggles to put Pied Piper's vision into words for a presentation without Erlich; later, he discovers an interesting connection between Peter and Gavin Belson.</description>
        <title>Silicon Valley</title>
        <summary>Silicon Valley 1x04 "Fiduciary Duties"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/silicon-valley/season/1/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="57996191398679200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140428T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140428T040000</dtend>
        <description>A chance encounter with a suspicious-looking individual leads Jane and Lisbon to uncover a vast human smuggling ring. Meanwhile, Lisbon remains tempted by Pike’s offer to move to D.C. with him.</description>
        <title>The Mentalist</title>
        <summary>The Mentalist 6x19 "Brown Eyed Girls"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-mentalist/season/6/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="308631398754800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140429T000000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140429T001100</dtend>
        <description>Finn and Jake discover that Clone James has been faking his own death to collect medals. Now there are 25 Jameses running amok!</description>
        <title>Adventure Time</title>
        <summary>Adventure Time 6x03 "James II"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/adventure-time/season/6/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="233071111398758400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140429T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140429T020000</dtend>
        <description>Sophia suspects Taylor is pregnant with Drake's baby. Sophia tells Emery and the two research Atrian pregnancies. Vartan stumbles upon the information and mistakenly believes Emery is pregnant, so he kidnaps her. Vega tasks Teri with finding the Iksen's key, which they need to complete the Suvek. Meanwhile, Roman and Castor testify before the Hwatab about the day the spaceship crashed. Also, Eric shares a nice moment with Julia.</description>
        <title>Star-Crossed</title>
        <summary>Star-Crossed 1x11 "Give Me a Torch"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/starcrossed/season/1/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="27531398762000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140429T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140429T024500</dtend>
        <description>Pete and Steve search for an artifact that makes a horseless chariot and a life-size chess piece come to life; Claudia combines artifacts in a desperate attempt to revive her sister.</description>
        <title>Warehouse 13</title>
        <summary>Warehouse 13 5x03 "A Faire to Remember"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/warehouse-13/season/5/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="736211398765600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140429T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140429T040000</dtend>
        <description>When an up-and-coming professional skateboarder is gunned down by a mysterious motorcyclist, Castle and Beckett are thrust into the world of extreme sports, where the death defying stunts aren’t the only thing that’s dangerous.</description>
        <title>Castle</title>
        <summary>Castle (2009) 6x21 "Law and Boarder"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/castle-2009/season/6/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="232881201398765600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140429T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140429T034500</dtend>
        <description>After a Politician in Prague is framed for a murder, Red suspects it’s the work of The Kingmaker a strategist behind the rise of some of the world’s most powerful politicians. While Red helps Liz and the FBI catch him, Liz uncovers a secret that Red’s been keeping from her.</description>
        <title>The Blacklist</title>
        <summary>The Blacklist 1x20 "The Kingmaker"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-blacklist/season/1/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1145181398844800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140430T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140430T020000</dtend>
        <description>Rachel is presented with a unique opportunity which could either take her career to the next level, or possibly kill it entirely. Meanwhile, Mercedes asks for Santana’s help finding a “new sound” for her latest single, and a wealthy New York socialite takes Blaine under her wing.</description>
        <title>Glee</title>
        <summary>Glee 5x18 "The Back-Up Plan"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/glee/season/5/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="191851201398844800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140430T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140430T020000</dtend>
        <description>[watched/collected]\n\nJust when there's no one left to trust, Agent Maria Hill returns to team up with Coulson as S.H.I.E.L.D. is being destroyed around them.</description>
        <title>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
        <summary>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. 1x20 "Nothing Personal"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/marvels-agents-of-shield/season/1/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6811221398844800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140430T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140430T014500</dtend>
        <description>When a Marine photographer disappears prior to providing his testimony in an Army court-martial hearing, the NCIS team investigates both the murder he witnessed as well as his current piece on military veterans who are homeless in the D.C. area. Meanwhile, Abby tries to help a young homeless woman reconnect with her family.</description>
        <title>NCIS</title>
        <summary>NCIS 11x22 "Shooter"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis/season/11/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1165221398848400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140430T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140430T024500</dtend>
        <description>Sam is convinced that the theft of software for a new unmanned aerial vehicle is connected with the disappearance of the lead engineer's 10-year-old daughter, a girl Sam once provided protection detail for in Saudi Arabia.</description>
        <title>NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
        <summary>NCIS: Los Angeles 5x22 "One More Chance"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis-los-angeles/season/5/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="96353221398848400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140430T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140430T023000</dtend>
        <description>Jess fears someone is trying to sabotage her first middle school dance and she enlists the gang to help her chaperone on the big night.</description>
        <title>New Girl</title>
        <summary>New Girl 3x22 "Dance"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/new-girl/season/3/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879131398852000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140430T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140430T040000</dtend>
        <description>Malvo flips the script on the blackmail operation, Molly sets a trap, and Gus debates whether he should come clean. Lester's return to work has complicated repercussions.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x03 "A Muddy Road"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113673211398852000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140430T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140430T040000</dtend>
        <description>Reese and Shaw are hunted by Decima; Greer uses Finch's greatest weakness -- his former fiancee -- to lure him out of hiding.</description>
        <title>Person of Interest</title>
        <summary>Person of Interest 3x21 "Beta"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/person-of-interest/season/3/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="163272211398931200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140501T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140501T014500</dtend>
        <description>After Slade threatens to take everything Oliver loves away, Oliver decides the fastest way to stop further bloodshed is to surrender to his enemy. Knowing that surrender will surely lead to Oliver's death, Diggle and Felicity go to extreme measures to keep Oliver from confronting Slade. Meanwhile, Thea considers leaving town, and Laurel resumes her crusade against Sebastian Blood. Finally, Slade unleashes his assault on Starling City.</description>
        <title>Arrow</title>
        <summary>Arrow 2x21 "City of Blood"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/arrow/season/2/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="161642191398931200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140501T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140501T020000</dtend>
        <description>As Miles, Monroe, Charlie and Connor rush to escape Austin, a confrontation with Texas Rangers separates Miles from the group. While out searching for Miles, Charlie is confronted by Neville who demands information on Jason’s whereabouts. As a wounded Miles faces increasingly hopeless circumstances, Aaron learns that the nanotech has been busy.</description>
        <title>Revolution</title>
        <summary>Revolution 2x19 "Happens"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/revolution/season/2/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113613111398933000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140501T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140501T020000</dtend>
        <description>When Dalia is rejected from the only college she applied to, Dallas is determined to help her daughter find her calling; George and Tessa go on a double date.</description>
        <title>Suburgatory</title>
        <summary>Suburgatory 3x11 "Dalia Nicole Smith"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suburgatory/season/3/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="25211398934800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140501T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140501T023000</dtend>
        <description>[watched/collected]\n\nPhil cannot handle the stress when he tells Claire an elaborate lie; Gloria is tasked with organizing this year's family portrait; Jay covertly enters Stella in a dog show.</description>
        <title>Modern Family</title>
        <summary>Modern Family 5x21 "Sleeper"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/modern-family/season/5/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="22923171398934800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140501T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140501T024500</dtend>
        <description>Clarke and Raven make contact with the Ark, and Abby guides Clarke through a dangerous procedure in a desperate move to save one of their own. Meanwhile, on the Ark, Abby is removed from the council, and former Chancellor Diana Sydney takes her place. Jaha reveals to Abby that there are not enough drop ships for everyone on the Ark to go down to Earth, and Kane begins to deal with his guilt over his recent decision.</description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x07 "Contents Under Pressure"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="347221399017600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140502T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140502T013000</dtend>
        <description>Professor Proton helps Sheldon deal with grief; Leonard gets into a competition with Penny; Bernadette and Amy prepare a "Star Wars Day" gift for the guys.</description>
        <title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
        <summary>The Big Bang Theory 7x22 "The Proton Transmogrification"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-big-bang-theory/season/7/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9310221399021200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140502T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140502T030000</dtend>
        <description>Cristina looks to Meredith for advice as she assesses her future at the hospital. Derek and Amelia work together on a difficult surgery involving conjoined twins. Meanwhile, Jo is spread too thin when she tries to work on several cases at once and Stephanie realizes the truth about Bailey’s bubble boy case.</description>
        <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
        <summary>Grey's Anatomy 10x22 "We Are Never Ever Getting Back Together"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/greys-anatomy/season/10/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713121399023000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140502T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140502T030000</dtend>
        <description>Meredith sets her sights on dating her student Bronwen's wealthy father, but hits a roadblock when Bronwen won't give her permission to go out with him.</description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x02 "Daddy Issues"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="164692221399024800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140502T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140502T040000</dtend>
        <description>Business becomes personal for Sherlock when he is forced to partner with his estranged brother, Mycroft, to solve a case with life-or-death consequences.</description>
        <title>Elementary</title>
        <summary>Elementary 2x22 "Paint It Black"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/elementary/season/2/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="115782121399104000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140503T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140503T020000</dtend>
        <description>When Carrie and Elliott are attending a party sponsored by the mayor, a group of criminals seizes control of the building, and demand a hefty ransom. It is up to Carrie to thwart their plans by playing from the Die Hard book.</description>
        <title>Unforgettable</title>
        <summary>Unforgettable 2x12 "Omega Hour"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/unforgettable/season/2/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="99383201399107600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140503T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140503T024500</dtend>
        <description>Nick does his best to educate Trubel on how best to handle the world she is learning about for the first time, and decides it best to bring her on a ride along with Hank. They find themselves investigating the homicide of a young woman that strikes a chord for Trubel. Meanwhile, Adalind makes a discovery that she hopes will lead her to regain something she has lost.</description>
        <title>Grimm</title>
        <summary>Grimm 3x20 "My Fair Wesen"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/grimm/season/3/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="844211399107600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140503T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140503T030000</dtend>
        <description>McGarrett and Catherine travel overseas to Afghanistan to stop the Taliban from harming a young boy whose family saved Catherine's life years ago.</description>
        <title>Hawaii Five-0</title>
        <summary>Hawaii Five-0 4x21 "Makani 'Olu a Holo Mālie"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hawaii-five0/season/4/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="166892101399111200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140503T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140503T034500</dtend>
        <description>The bond between Hannibal and Will grows after Will demonstrates his willingness to go to dark places, a shift that does not go unnoticed by Jack. Jack and the FBI team investigate a tableau made of Randal Tier and his animal exoskeleton, fully realized as the vicious hunter he yearned to be. Hannibal advises Margot Verger regarding her concerns over her brother Mason’s violent nature, a fear that intensifies when Mason demonstrates how he has trained pigs to consume human flesh. Will agrees to an interview with Freddie Lounds for her upcoming book, and learns that she is looking into his allegations of Hannibal’s possible guilt.</description>
        <title>Hannibal</title>
        <summary>Hannibal 2x10 "Naka-Choko"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hannibal/season/2/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="73510181399275000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T003000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T010000</dtend>
        <description>When budget cuts result in Stan getting fired, his work experience is considered classified and he is forced to take a job at the store Steve manages; Roger makes a bet with an irritating coffee shop musician (Robin Thicke).</description>
        <title>American Dad!</title>
        <summary>American Dad! 10x18 "Permanent Record Wrecker"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/american-dad/season/10/episode/18</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="106463201399276800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T020000</dtend>
        <description>With Mary Margaret in labor and due to give birth at any moment, the residents of Storybrooke go on high alert in an attempt to ensure that Zelena doesn't try to steal her newborn baby for use in her ultimate game plan to turn back time and change her destiny -- while obliterating Regina's existence. Meanwhile, in the land of Oz of the past, Glinda tries to convince Zelena to fight her evil tendencies and join her and her sister witches as a protector of Oz. But the appearance of a young girl from Kansas could turn out to be her undoing.</description>
        <title>Once Upon a Time</title>
        <summary>Once Upon a Time (2011) 3x20 "Kansas"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/once-upon-a-time-2011/season/3/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6525201399276800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T012500</dtend>
        <description>Homer wakes up in a world where his family and everyone in Springfield are made of Lego, and he must "put together" how he got there, and figure out how to get home before he's stuck in a world of bricks forever.</description>
        <title>The Simpsons</title>
        <summary>The Simpsons 25x20 "Brick Like Me"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-simpsons/season/25/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23908191399280400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T030000</dtend>
        <description>The Ship of the Imagination embarks on a journey through space and time to grasp how the autobiography of the Earth is written in its atoms, its oceans, its continents and all living things. Later, American geologist Marie Tharp creates the first true map of Earth’s ocean floor, and discovers microscopic life that exists deep beneath the ocean</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x09 "The Lost Worlds of Planet Earth"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="334671399280400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T030000</dtend>
        <description>Jane and Grayson spend the night together; Owen defends the Mayor of Malibu; Jane represents a teenage girl in need of a bone marrow match; Kim agrees to let Stacy watch her infant son.</description>
        <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
        <summary>Drop Dead Diva 6x07 "Sister Act"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/drop-dead-diva/season/6/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395451399280400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T030000</dtend>
        <description>Cersei and Tywin plan the Crown's next move. Daenerys discusses future plans. Jon Snow begins a new mission.</description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x05 "First of His Name"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="3385201399280400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T030000</dtend>
        <description>When Alicia has a chance encounter with a charming entrepreneur during jury duty, she begins to consider options outside her marriage and seeks the advice of her mother. Meanwhile, Diane's friends come to her for legal advice when their son is accused of selling drugs on the Internet.</description>
        <title>The Good Wife</title>
        <summary>The Good Wife 5x20 "The Deep Web"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-good-wife/season/5/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028231399284000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T040000</dtend>
        <description>Marisol discovers some shocking news about her fiancé Nicholas and Opal. Dissatisfied with the doctor that Didi’s provided for Kenneth, Rosie takes Kenneth to a specialist who provides them newfound hope. Carmen prepares for her performance debut in front of industry bigwigs, but when reality hits she struggles to perform. Genevieve tries to show her support by inviting Zoila to a luncheon. Increasingly wary of Adrian’s behavior, Evelyn finds comfort elsewhere. Valentina struggles to get over Remi.</description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x03 "Dangerous Liaisons"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="20741399284000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T040000</dtend>
        <description>Sterling Cooper and Partners prepares for a guest; Don contacts an old friend; Roger deals with problems at home; Peggy is underestimated.</description>
        <title>Mad Men</title>
        <summary>Mad Men 7x04 "The Monolith"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/mad-men/season/7/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23332151399284000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T033000</dtend>
        <description>Erlich taps a graffiti artist to design Pied Piper's logo, with predictably controversial results. Meanwhile, Richard learns he doesn't have much time to prepare for a live demonstration at TechCrunch Disrupt; Gavin Belson and Peter Gregory have an unexpected encounter; and Jared works on the company's efficiency.</description>
        <title>Silicon Valley</title>
        <summary>Silicon Valley 1x05 "Signaling Risk"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/silicon-valley/season/1/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="57996201399284000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140505T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140505T040000</dtend>
        <description>Jane’s freedom is at stake when a grand jury is empanelled to decide if he should be tried for the murder of Red John. Meanwhile, Lisbon tries to find out how Jane feels about the possibility of her leaving Austin with Agent Pike, and Cho and Abbott follow new leads in the human smuggling ring they recently uncovered.</description>
        <title>The Mentalist</title>
        <summary>The Mentalist 6x20 "Il Tavolo Bianco"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-mentalist/season/6/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="308641399359600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140506T000000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140506T001100</dtend>
        <description>Finn doesn't like any of the new arms the princesses give him, so he builds a tower into space to find his dad and get his old arm back. But are his hopes up a little too high?</description>
        <title>Adventure Time</title>
        <summary>Adventure Time 6x04 "The Tower "</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/adventure-time/season/6/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199911399363200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140506T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140506T014500</dtend>
        <description>After four years off the grid, Jack is apprehended in London by the CIA – on the very day that President James Heller arrives. As the President faces political pressure over a US drone program run from a UK-based base, only disgraced agent Kate Morgan suspects that Jack's capture was all too easy.</description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x01 "Live Another Day: 11:00 A.M. - 12:00 P.M."</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199921399363200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140506T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140506T014500</dtend>
        <description>Jack and Chloe are on the trail of a hacker who might lead them to whoever is behind an assassination attempt on President Heller... but Kate is hot on Jack's trail.</description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x02 "Live Another Day: 12:00 P.M. - 1:00 P.M."</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="233071121399363200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140506T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140506T020000</dtend>
        <description>After Roman and Drake discover the Trags are building a bomb known as a Suvec, they realize they need help and turn to an unexpected source – Grayson. Emery enlists Sophia and Lukas to help them smuggle the Suvek out of the sector, which ultimately puts all of them in danger. Meanwhile, Teri continues her mission.</description>
        <title>Star-Crossed</title>
        <summary>Star-Crossed 1x12 "This Trick May Chance to Scathe You"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/starcrossed/season/1/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="27541399366800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140506T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140506T024500</dtend>
        <description>Pete, Myka and Artie help Pete's ex-girlfriend track an object that sucks them all into a Telenovela.</description>
        <title>Warehouse 13</title>
        <summary>Warehouse 13 5x04 "Savage Seduction"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/warehouse-13/season/5/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="736221399370400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140506T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140506T040000</dtend>
        <description>A secret investigation conducted by Beckett related to her mother's murder goes awry when a man she has been surveilling is killed. When evidence links Beckett to the victim, she and Castle become the targets of a manhunt that puts both of them in grave danger.</description>
        <title>Castle</title>
        <summary>Castle (2009) 6x22 "Veritas"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/castle-2009/season/6/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="232881211399370400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140506T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140506T034500</dtend>
        <description>Knowing the truth about her father, Liz refuses to work with Red; Red brings the FBI a compelling case; Liz reveals what she knows about Tom's life.</description>
        <title>The Blacklist</title>
        <summary>The Blacklist 1x21 "Berlin"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-blacklist/season/1/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1145191399449600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140507T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140507T020000</dtend>
        <description>Santana helps Rachel do damage control for her flagging public image; Kurt tries to help a home for retired Broadway performers with their production of Peter Pan; to prove he is responsible, Sam adopts a dog - despite Mercedes’ objections.</description>
        <title>Glee</title>
        <summary>Glee 5x19 "Old Dogs, New Tricks"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/glee/season/5/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="191851211399449600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140507T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140507T020000</dtend>
        <description>Ward's betrayal and Hydra's shocking secrets are revealed as Coulson's team goes undercover on a mission that leaves no one unscathed.</description>
        <title>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
        <summary>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. 1x21 "Ragtag"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/marvels-agents-of-shield/season/1/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6811231399449600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140507T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140507T014500</dtend>
        <description>Director Vance gives DiNozzo a special assignment to bring home an Admiral’s daughter from Paris, but he must turn to his NCIS team for help after he enters a controversial crime scene.</description>
        <title>NCIS</title>
        <summary>NCIS 11x23 "The Admiral's Daughter"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis/season/11/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1165231399453200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140507T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140507T024500</dtend>
        <description>When a news reporter announces the group responsible for the deadly explosion at a military-sponsored charity event, the team must investigate her claims and search for the attacker.</description>
        <title>NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
        <summary>NCIS: Los Angeles 5x23 "Exposure"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis-los-angeles/season/5/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="96353231399453200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140507T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140507T023000</dtend>
        <description>Jess and Nick invite the gang along with them on a cruise they booked while still together as a couple. Coach tries to suppress his fear of boating, Schmidt attempts to win back Cece and Winston tries to mend Jess and Nick’s fractured relationship.</description>
        <title>New Girl</title>
        <summary>New Girl 3x23 "Cruise"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/new-girl/season/3/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879141399456800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140507T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140507T040000</dtend>
        <description>When Gus tries to right a wrong, Malvo embraces his alter ego. Lester finds himself in a surprising situation, and Molly uncovers a promising lead.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x04 "Eating the Blame"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113673221399456800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140507T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140507T040000</dtend>
        <description>The machine sends the team five different numbers to investigate when an unknown entity blocks details about an impending catastrophic event; Root's hackers arrive in New York.</description>
        <title>Person of Interest</title>
        <summary>Person of Interest 3x22 "A House Divided"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/person-of-interest/season/3/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="163272221399536000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140508T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140508T014500</dtend>
        <description>Oliver rallies his team as Slade’s soldiers attack the city. Felicity gets a call from S.T.A.R. Labs with game-changing news and Thea comes face-to-face with her father – Malcolm Merlyn.</description>
        <title>Arrow</title>
        <summary>Arrow 2x22 "Streets of Fire"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/arrow/season/2/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="161642201399536000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140508T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140508T020000</dtend>
        <description>Truman, empowered with new authority from the President, launches a mustard gas attack designed to kill Miles and Monroe. To Rachel's disappointment, Miles agrees to join Monroe in a ruthless plot to beat the Patriots at their own game. As Neville faces his own challenge from the Patriots, Aaron grows increasingly alarmed by the power of the nanotech.</description>
        <title>Revolution</title>
        <summary>Revolution 2x20 "Tomorrowland"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/revolution/season/2/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113613121399537800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140508T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140508T020000</dtend>
        <description>Tessa struggles with the budget while planning Lisa and Malik's wedding; June warns Tessa to stay away from Ryan; Malik turns to George when his family decides to boycott the wedding; Sheila gives Lisa advice.</description>
        <title>Suburgatory</title>
        <summary>Suburgatory 3x12 "Les Lucioles"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suburgatory/season/3/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="25221399539600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140508T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140508T023000</dtend>
        <description>Jay, Gloria and Manny challenge one another to try something new; Mitch and Cam sell a couple of their prized possessions to fund the wedding; the kids play a joke on Phil and Claire.</description>
        <title>Modern Family</title>
        <summary>Modern Family 5x22 "Message Received"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/modern-family/season/5/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="22923181399539600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140508T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140508T024500</dtend>
        <description>Clarke and Bellamy go on a mission to find supplies for approaching winter. Some of the 100 accidentally eat nuts with powerfully hallucinogenic properties and lose their grasp on reality.  Meanwhile, Octavia seizes the opportunity to help a friend escape, and a terrifying event brings Clarke and Bellamy closer. On the Ark, Commander Shumway secretly assigns one of the 100 to kill one of his own, and the treacherous actions of Diane Sydney are revealed.</description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x08 "Day Trip"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="347231399622400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140509T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140509T013000</dtend>
        <description>A bad day compels Penny to re-evaluate her choices -- including Leonard; Bernadette and Howard must care for Mrs. Wolowitz; Sheldon gives Raj advice on relationships.</description>
        <title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
        <summary>The Big Bang Theory 7x23 "The Gorilla Dissolution"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-big-bang-theory/season/7/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9310231399626000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140509T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140509T030000</dtend>
        <description>With Derek away, Meredith spends time with Amelia and finds out her true feelings about her time in Seattle. Bailey deals with the ramifications of her actions and Callie receives devastating news. Meanwhile, the residents panic after hearing that one of them will be fired.</description>
        <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
        <summary>Grey's Anatomy 10x23 "Everything I Try to Do, Nothing Seems to Turn Out Right"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/greys-anatomy/season/10/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713131399627800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140509T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140509T030000</dtend>
        <description>When the faculty faces district teacher evaluations, Principal Carl asks Meredith to assist Ginny with student engagement. Meanwhile, Lily tries to convince Irene that Meredith is taking advantage of her friendship.</description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x03 "Evaluation Day"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="164692231399629600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140509T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140509T040000</dtend>
        <description>Holmes and Watson come into contact with MI-6, the British intelligence agency, when a standard murder investigation turns out to have international and political implications. Meanwhile, in the wake of a crisis, Watson reevaluates her relationships with Sherlock and his brother, Mycroft.</description>
        <title>Elementary</title>
        <summary>Elementary 2x23 "Art in the Blood"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/elementary/season/2/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="115782131399708800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140510T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140510T020000</dtend>
        <description>Carrie's high school reunion is suddenly cut short when an alum shows up dead. Carrie has to remember back 22 years to understand the events that led to this crime.</description>
        <title>Unforgettable</title>
        <summary>Unforgettable 2x13 "Reunion"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/unforgettable/season/2/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="99383211399712400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140510T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140510T024500</dtend>
        <description>Nick and Hank are called to investigate a double homicide, and quickly learn the victims were from a special section of the Verrat tasked with finding rare objects pertaining to the Wesen world. Trubel gets involved with a mysterious father-and-son tandem that crossed the country in a desperate attempt to deliver invaluable cargo to "the Portland Grimm." Meanwhile, Captain Renard begins to grow suspicious of Adalind's recent behavior and quietly decides to put extra eyes on her.</description>
        <title>Grimm</title>
        <summary>Grimm 3x21 "The Inheritance"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/grimm/season/3/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="844221399712400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140510T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140510T030000</dtend>
        <description>When Grover's daughter is kidnapped by an old nemesis, he is forced to help steal $100 million in order to get her back. Meanwhile, Wo Fat escapes prison and heads back to Oahu.</description>
        <title>Hawaii Five-0</title>
        <summary>Hawaii Five-0 4x22 "O ka Pili'Ohana ka 'Oi"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hawaii-five0/season/4/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="166892111399716000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140510T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140510T034500</dtend>
        <description>Jack and his team discover the truth of Freddie Lounds' disappearance; Will tells Alana to arm herself; Mason suspects his sister intends to usurp him; Hannibal shows Will how much Abigail reminded him of his sister.</description>
        <title>Hannibal</title>
        <summary>Hannibal 2x11 "Kō No Mono"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hannibal/season/2/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="73510191399879800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T003000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T010000</dtend>
        <description>Hayley takes a job as an intern at a local news station for a reporter -- who is actually Roger in disguise.</description>
        <title>American Dad!</title>
        <summary>American Dad! 10x19 "News Glances With Genevieve Vavance"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/american-dad/season/10/episode/19</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="106463211399881600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T020000</dtend>
        <description>While Mary Margaret and David celebrate the naming of their son at a coronation in Granny's Diner, Emma and Hook are pulled into Zelena's time portal and find themselves in the Enchanted Forest of the past. But in their quest to discover a way back, they must be careful not to change ANYTHING or risk altering the lives of their friends and family - as well as their very own existence.</description>
        <title>Once Upon a Time</title>
        <summary>Once Upon a Time (2011) 3x21 "Snow Drifts"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/once-upon-a-time-2011/season/3/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="106463221399881600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T020000</dtend>
        <description>While Mary Margaret and David celebrate the naming of their son at a coronation in Granny's Diner, Emma and Hook are pulled into Zelena's time portal and find themselves in the Enchanted Forest of the past. But in their quest to discover a way back, they must be careful not to change ANYTHING or risk altering the lives of their friends and family - as well as their very own existence.</description>
        <title>Once Upon a Time</title>
        <summary>Once Upon a Time (2011) 3x22 "There's No Place Like Home"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/once-upon-a-time-2011/season/3/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6525211399881600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T012500</dtend>
        <description>Marge swears off befriending any more couples when Homer offends their charming new British neighbors, but when Lisa declares that she, too, doesn’t need friends, Marge reconsiders.</description>
        <title>The Simpsons</title>
        <summary>The Simpsons 25x21 "Pay Pal"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-simpsons/season/25/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="239081101399885200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T030000</dtend>
        <description>Travel to 19th century England and meet Michael Faraday, a child of poverty who grew up to invent the motor and the generator. His ideas about electricity and discovery of magnetic fields changed the world and paved the way for future scientists to make giant strides in the world of high technology and instantaneous communication</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x10 "The Electric Boy"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="334681399885200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
        <summary>Drop Dead Diva 6x08 "Identity Crisis"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/drop-dead-diva/season/6/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395461399885200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T030000</dtend>
        <description>Stannis and Davos set sail; Dany meets with supplicants; Tyrion faces down his father.</description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x06 "The Laws of Gods and Men"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="3385211399885200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T030000</dtend>
        <description>Alicia manages the fallout when her client's insensitive statements to the press threaten the fate of a multi-billion dollar merger. Meanwhile, Diane faces a potential conflict of interest when she and Louis Canning are on opposite sides of a class action suit involving a pharmaceutical company. Also, Eli learns the truth about Alicia and Peter's relationship.</description>
        <title>The Good Wife</title>
        <summary>The Good Wife 5x21 "The One Percent"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-good-wife/season/5/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028241399888800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T040000</dtend>
        <description>Marisol believes Nicholas could be hiding something from her. Genevieve wants Zoila to bring a date with her to try and make Pablo jealous. Evelyn wants Adrian out of the house to spend some time with Tony. Carmen and Rosie fall out over Carmen's new job. Valentina and Ethan's relationship develops. Genevieve hears something shocking about Remi.</description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x04 "Crimes of the Heart"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="20751399888800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T040000</dtend>
        <description>Don has a visitor from his past. Stan embarrasses a superior. Peggy helps Ginsberg with a problem. Harry finds that he has a new ally at the agency.</description>
        <title>Mad Men</title>
        <summary>Mad Men 7x05 "The Runaways"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/mad-men/season/7/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23332161399888800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T033000</dtend>
        <description>Richard feels threatened when the team hires “The Carver” a hacker with a notorious reputation, to help with Pied Piper’s cloud. Jared finds himself taken for a ride when he seeks out Peter Gregory’s signature. Erlich and Dinesh compete for the attention of Tara, Gilfoyle’s visiting girlfriend. Later, Dinesh faces a sexual dilemma.</description>
        <title>Silicon Valley</title>
        <summary>Silicon Valley 1x06 "Third Party Insourcing"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/silicon-valley/season/1/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="57996211399888800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140512T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140512T040000</dtend>
        <description>With time running out to save the victims of a kidnapping ring before they are transported overseas, Jane and Lisbon zero in on the criminal enterprise’s mastermind. Meanwhile, Lisbon decides if she will move to D.C. with Agent Pike.</description>
        <title>The Mentalist</title>
        <summary>The Mentalist 6x21 "Black Hearts"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-mentalist/season/6/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="308651399964400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140513T000000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140513T001100</dtend>
        <description>Once a month, while Jake's asleep, his tail stretches out of the tree house to go work as a clown in a traveling bug circus.[</description>
        <title>Adventure Time</title>
        <summary>Adventure Time 6x05 "Sad Face"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/adventure-time/season/6/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199931399968000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140513T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140513T014500</dtend>
        <description>As the hunt continues for Jack Bauer, the terror threat is intensifying, much to the chagrin of the CIA and Kate Morgan. Across town, President James Heller prepares to address Parliament in an attempt to heal recent wounds with the British, and to preserve his legacy. Meanwhile, Margot - a homegrown British terrorist seeking to avenge her husband's death - proves she is willing to make any sacrifice for her mission.</description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x03 "Live Another Day: 1:00 P.M. - 2:00 P.M."</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="929231399968000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140513T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140513T020000</dtend>
        <description>The Jeffersonian team investigates the death of Brian Thomas, the head swim coach at a community college, whose remains were found dumped at the bottom of a well. When possible suspects tell Brennan and Sweets that Brian may have been having an affair, the team digs a little deeper only to find details of Brian's secret life. Meanwhile, Sweets fills in for Booth in the investigation while Booth prepares to testify before a Congressional sub-committee and the Jeffersonian team gets a new intern who catches Sweets' attention.</description>
        <title>Bones</title>
        <summary>Bones 9x23 "The Drama in the Queen"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bones/season/9/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="233071131399968000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140513T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140513T020000</dtend>
        <description>After Roman is badly hurt, Emery turns to an unexpected ally for help. Meanwhile, Grayson, Drake, Sophia and Lukas race to find the stolen Suvek before the Trags can activate it. However, Vega is a step ahead of them and sets off the Suvek in the middle of a Marti Gras parade. Teri is shocked when she overhears Vega ordering the death of her friends. Gloria discovers Taylor’s secret and shares one of her own.</description>
        <title>Star-Crossed</title>
        <summary>Star-Crossed 1x13 "Passion Lends Them Power"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/starcrossed/season/1/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="27551399971600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140513T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140513T024500</dtend>
        <description>Valda tries to move the warehouse to China and use Claudia's comatose sister as a puppet caretaker.</description>
        <title>Warehouse 13</title>
        <summary>Warehouse 13 5x05 "Cangku Shisi"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/warehouse-13/season/5/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="736231399975200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140513T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140513T040000</dtend>
        <description>Castle and Beckett's long-awaited wedding is almost here, but when a shocking surprise threatens to ruin the big day, they are sent on a wild mission filled with masked men, angry bikers and a charming ne'er-do-well from Beckett's past.</description>
        <title>Castle</title>
        <summary>Castle (2009) 6x23 "For Better or Worse"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/castle-2009/season/6/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="232881221399975200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140513T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140513T034500</dtend>
        <description>With the crashing of the mysterious prisoner transport plane, the city is on lock down as the authorities are on the hunt for all the escapees. Meanwhile, with Red  in custody, Liz uses her power to get him out since he is their best chance at finding all the suspects. Elsewhere, their main objective is to track down Berlin, a prisoner on the plane who is somehow involved.</description>
        <title>The Blacklist</title>
        <summary>The Blacklist 1x22 "Berlin: Conclusion"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-blacklist/season/1/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1145201400054400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140514T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140514T020000</dtend>
        <description>Rachel meets a famous television writer, whose eccentric personality catches Rachel off guard. Meanwhile, Sam and Mercedes deal with the pressure of commitment as their careers take off, and the time has finally come for Blaine’s big showcase with June Dolloway at NYADA.</description>
        <title>Glee</title>
        <summary>Glee 5x20 "The Untitled Rachel Berry Project"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/glee/season/5/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="191851221400054400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140514T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140514T020000</dtend>
        <description>Dark secrets are revealed as Coulson and his team put everything on the line to stop Garrett and the forces of Hydra.</description>
        <title>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.</title>
        <summary>Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. 1x22 "Beginning of the End"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/marvels-agents-of-shield/season/1/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6811241400054400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140514T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140514T014500</dtend>
        <description>The NCIS team investigates whether a fire on a U.S. Navy ship that served as a secret detention site for indicted terrorists was accidental or an intentional diversion for an escape. Meanwhile, Gibbs travels to his childhood home following news of his father’s passing.</description>
        <title>NCIS</title>
        <summary>NCIS 11x24 "Honor Thy Father"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis/season/11/episode/24</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1165241400058000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140514T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140514T024500</dtend>
        <description>When the NCIS: Los Angeles team and DEA uncover the cartel's plans to slyly transport billions of dollars’ worth of cocaine from Colombia to the U.S. using a submarine, Callen and Sam must quickly locate the missing vessel. Meanwhile, Hetty is called to Washington in the aftermath of the controversial mission in Afghanistan.</description>
        <title>NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
        <summary>NCIS: Los Angeles 5x24 "Deep Trouble (1)"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/ncis-los-angeles/season/5/episode/24</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879151400061600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140514T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140514T040000</dtend>
        <description>When Lester has a close call, Molly makes an unorthodox decision. Gus weighs some neighborly advice, and Malvo gets what he wants.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x05 "The Six Ungraspables"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113673231400061600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140514T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140514T040000</dtend>
        <description>The team work to stop Samaritan from coming online and targeting them; the battle against Vigilance reaches a conclusion.</description>
        <title>Person of Interest</title>
        <summary>Person of Interest 3x23 "Deus Ex Machina"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/person-of-interest/season/3/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="163272231400140800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140515T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140515T014500</dtend>
        <description>Slade moves forward with his plan to kill one more person in Oliver’s life. While Oliver has fought all year to be more than the killer he once was, when Slade kidnaps someone close to Oliver’s heart, Oliver is pushed to the edge and realizes sometimes it takes doing the unthinkable to stop the monster. Meanwhile, Diggle takes on Amanda Waller with a little help from some friends, and Thea turns to Roy in her time of need.</description>
        <title>Arrow</title>
        <summary>Arrow 2x23 "Unthinkable"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/arrow/season/2/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="161642211400140800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140515T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140515T020000</dtend>
        <description>United by their desire to take the Patriots down, Neville and Monroe form an uneasy alliance. As Rachel comes face-to-face with the nano-tech while searching for Aaron, things don't go according to plan for Miles, Charlie and Gene when they try to steal the Patriots' supply of mustard gas.</description>
        <title>Revolution</title>
        <summary>Revolution 2x21 "Memorial Day"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/revolution/season/2/episode/21</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="113613131400142600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140515T013000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140515T020000</dtend>
        <description>When Tessa joins a knitting circle, the age of her new friends surprises George; George writes a song dedicated to his muse; Malik and Lisa bicker.</description>
        <title>Suburgatory</title>
        <summary>Suburgatory 3x13 "Stiiiiiiill Horny"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suburgatory/season/3/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="25231400144400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140515T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140515T023000</dtend>
        <description>A series of crises on Mitch and Cam's wedding day put Pepper to the test; Phil gets an eye procedure before the celebration; Claire embraces the role of best woman.</description>
        <title>Modern Family</title>
        <summary>Modern Family 5x23 "The Wedding (1)"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/modern-family/season/5/episode/23</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="22923191400144400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140515T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140515T024500</dtend>
        <description>Clarke and Finn attempt to broker peace with the Grounders but all hell breaks loose when Bellamy, Jasper and Raven show up armed and ready for battle. Octavia and Lincoln grow closer. Meanwhile, tragedy strikes during the Unity Day celebration on the Ark.</description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x09 "Unity Day"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="347241400227200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140516T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140516T013000</dtend>
        <description>Sheldon is forced to confront an uncertain future and considers a major move. Meanwhile, Raj and Emily take it to the next level, and Mrs. Wolowitz’s injury is a major headache for Howard and Bernadette.</description>
        <title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
        <summary>The Big Bang Theory 7x24 "The Status Quo Combustion"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-big-bang-theory/season/7/episode/24</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9310241400230800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140516T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140516T030000</dtend>
        <description>The doctors of Grey Sloan Memorial Hospital bid an emotional farewell to the beloved Cristina Yang. A possible act of terrorism rocks Seattle and causes chaos at the hospital. Meanwhile, Meredith makes a life changing decision and one doctor receives shocking news.</description>
        <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
        <summary>Grey's Anatomy 10x24 "Fear (of the Unknown)"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/greys-anatomy/season/10/episode/24</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713141400232600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140516T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140516T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x04 "The 6th Grade Lock-In"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="164692241400234400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140516T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140516T040000</dtend>
        <description>Rising tension between Sherlock and Joan brings their partnership to a crossroads, but they endeavor to put their differences aside while they help Sherlock's brother, Mycroft, who faces accusations of treason and murder.</description>
        <title>Elementary</title>
        <summary>Elementary 2x24 "The Grand Experiment"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/elementary/season/2/episode/24</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="99383221400317200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140517T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140517T024500</dtend>
        <description>It's Monroe and Rosalee's big day and their joy will only be matched by unexpected heartache for those around them. Nick and Juliette make a startling realization that could shake their relationship to its core. Meanwhile, Adalind proceeds with a delicately laid plan that leads to a catastrophic event that will alter the course of Nick's journey.</description>
        <title>Grimm</title>
        <summary>Grimm 3x22 "Blond Ambition"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/grimm/season/3/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="166892121400320800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140517T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140517T034500</dtend>
        <description>During a therapy session, Will shares a vision of how he would kill Hannibal; feeling impatient, Jack brings in a surprise witness to help Will catch Hannibal.</description>
        <title>Hannibal</title>
        <summary>Hannibal 2x12 "Tome-wan"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hannibal/season/2/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="73510201400484600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T003000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T010000</dtend>
        <description>Hayley meets a millionaire who tries to help her move on from her heartbreak; Snot and Steve make a discovery.</description>
        <title>American Dad!</title>
        <summary>American Dad! 10x20 "The Longest Distance Relationship"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/american-dad/season/10/episode/20</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="6525221400486400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T012500</dtend>
        <description>Bart is plagued with guilt when he wins the annual “last day of school” race around Springfield Elementary, with assistance from Nelson, who beats up frontrunner Milhouse. Meanwhile, Homer tries to bring back the annual 4th of July fireworks display after it’s canceled for budget reasons.</description>
        <title>The Simpsons</title>
        <summary>The Simpsons 25x22 "The Yellow Badge of Cowardge"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-simpsons/season/25/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="239081111400490000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T030000</dtend>
        <description>Must we die? Are there beings in the cosmos who live forever, traveling on an endless journey down the river of time? Red dwarf stars live for trillions of years. What would intelligent beings do if they had an eternity to develop their understanding of the universe? Join Neil on a trip to the Cosmic Calendar of the Future and the historic events on Earth that happen in the first seconds of January 1st of the new Cosmic Year.</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x11 "The Immortals"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="334691400490000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Drop Dead Diva</title>
        <summary>Drop Dead Diva 6x09 "Hope and Glory"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/drop-dead-diva/season/6/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395471400490000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T030000</dtend>
        <description>Tyrion gains an unlikely ally; Daario asks Dany to allow him to do what he does best; Jon's warnings about the vulnerability of the Wall are ignored; Brienne follows a new lead.</description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x07 "Mockingbird"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="3385221400490000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T030000</dtend>
        <description>An open feed from a camera mistakenly left on after a teleconferenced deposition between the lawyers of Florrick/Agos and Lockhart/Gardner reveals a threat to the firm that Alicia and Cary never saw coming. Meanwhile, the fate of Lockhart/Gardner hangs in the balance as Louis Canning vies for a larger role. Also, Alicia entrusts Zach's high school graduation party to Jackie and Veronica.</description>
        <title>The Good Wife</title>
        <summary>The Good Wife 5x22 "A Weird Year"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-good-wife/season/5/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028251400493600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x05 "The Bad Seed"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="20761400493600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T040000</dtend>
        <description>Peggy collects research for a pitch; Pete receives an invitation to an exclusive club; Joan is eager to spend time with her friend.</description>
        <title>Mad Men</title>
        <summary>Mad Men 7x06 "The Strategy"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/mad-men/season/7/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23332171400493600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T033000</dtend>
        <description>At TechCrunch Disrupt, Richard feels the pressure to finish his demo, but finds himself distracted by a girl he dated briefly, who’s now spreading rumors about him. Jared worries that Monica is taking his place in the company. Dinesh develops a crush on a girl at a neighboring booth. Erlich’s scandalous past connection to one of the judges threatens Pied Piper’s chances.</description>
        <title>Silicon Valley</title>
        <summary>Silicon Valley 1x07 "Proof of Concept"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/silicon-valley/season/1/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="57996221400493600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140519T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140519T040000</dtend>
        <description>A new lead in a cold case requires Lisbon to delay her plans to leave for Washington, D.C., giving Jane time to finally come to terms with his feelings for her and decide on a course of action.</description>
        <title>The Mentalist</title>
        <summary>The Mentalist 6x22 "Blue Bird"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-mentalist/season/6/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199941400572800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140520T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140520T014500</dtend>
        <description>The terror threat escalates as Jack heads for the U.S. Embassy with the CIA closing in on him. Meanwhile, Margot asserts her authority with unthinkable force; President Heller makes an impassioned speech to Parliament; and Kate takes matters into her own hands.</description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x04 "Live Another Day: 2:00 P.M. - 3:00 P.M."</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="929241400572800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140520T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140520T020000</dtend>
        <description>The team investigates the death of a man who had offered Booth information on a possible government cover-up related to a previous case, but was killed before their meeting took place. As Booth and the Jeffersonian team dig deeper into the burgeoning conspiracy surrounding the man’s death, it’s evident Booth may be in over his head, and his future with the FBI is put in question.</description>
        <title>Bones</title>
        <summary>Bones 9x24 "The Recluse in the Recliner"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bones/season/9/episode/24</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="27561400576400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140520T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140520T024500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Warehouse 13</title>
        <summary>Warehouse 13 5x06 "Endless"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/warehouse-13/season/5/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879161400666400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140521T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140521T040000</dtend>
        <description>Malvo executes his master plan, while Lester attempts to craft one of his own. Gus and Molly team up in Duluth.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x06 "Buridan's Ass"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="161642221400745600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140522T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140522T020000</dtend>
        <description>Miles, Charlie and Monroe launch an attack on the Patriots, but must improvise a risky new plan in order to halt the oncoming war between California and Texas. Out for revenge, Neville sets his sights on President Davis. Meanwhile, Aaron and Rachel’s efforts to save Priscilla from the nano-tech has unexpected consequences.</description>
        <title>Revolution</title>
        <summary>Revolution 2x22 "Declaration of Independence"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/revolution/season/2/episode/22</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="25241400749200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140522T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140522T023000</dtend>
        <description>Chaos forces Mitch and Cam to move from one contingency plan to another, but an unexpected turn of events allows the day to move forward.</description>
        <title>Modern Family</title>
        <summary>Modern Family 5x24 "The Wedding (2)"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/modern-family/season/5/episode/24</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="229231101400749200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140522T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140522T024500</dtend>
        <description>Murphy returns to camp claiming to have been held captive and tortured by the Grounders, and Clarke and Bellamy have very different opinions on how to handle his return. Octavia sneaks away to find Lincoln and returns with a serious warning for the 100. Meanwhile, a mysterious virus strikes camp forcing many to be quarantined, and Jasper pulls off a heroic move.</description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x10 "I Am Become Death"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713151400837400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140523T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140523T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x05 "Found Money"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="166892131400925600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140524T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140524T034500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Hannibal</title>
        <summary>Hannibal 2x13 "Mizumono"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/hannibal/season/2/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="239081121401094800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140526T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140526T030000</dtend>
        <description>Neil traces the surprisingly lengthy history of the awareness of global warming and the technology of alternative energy, taking the Ship of the Imagination to intervene at some critical time travel nodes. We conclude with a breath-taking vision of the magnificent future that is scientifically and technically within our grasp, if we will only awaken from our stupor and seize it.</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x12 "The World Set Free"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028261401098400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140526T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140526T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x06 "Private Lives"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="20771401098400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140526T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140526T040000</dtend>
        <description>Don is troubled by a letter; Peggy may seek a new future on a risky venture; Roger receives a phone call; Pete and Cutler butt heads.</description>
        <title>Mad Men</title>
        <summary>Mad Men 7x07 "Waterloo"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/mad-men/season/7/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199951401177600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140527T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140527T014500</dtend>
        <description>An unlikely duo joins forces to forestall an impending attack. The terrorist reveals her demands. The President orders a military lockdown, but it may be too late.</description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x05 "Live Another Day: 3:00 P.M. - 4:00 P.M."</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879171401271200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140528T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140528T040000</dtend>
        <description>Malvo seeks answers, while Lester finagles a few of his own. Molly and Gus try to get past a setback in the investigation.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x07 "Who Shaves the Barber?"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="229231111401354000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140529T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140529T024500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x11 "TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713161401442200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140530T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140530T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x06 "Evaluation Day"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="239081131401699600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140602T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140602T030000</dtend>
        <description>We’ve traveled such a long way together, from deep inside the heart of an atom clear out to the cosmic horizon, from the beginning of time to the distant future…We’re ready to perform an experiment. It’s a thought experiment so all you’ll need is brain. If you do it correctly, the vastness and mystery of the cosmos is the inescapable result. We witness Martin Behaim creating the first globe of the world mere months before Columbus discovers another continent or two.</description>
        <title>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey</title>
        <summary>Cosmos: A Spacetime Odyssey 1x13 "Unafraid of the Dark"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/cosmos-a-spacetime-odyssey/season/1/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395481401699600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140602T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140602T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x08 "The Mountain and the Viper"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028271401703200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140602T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140602T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x07</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23332181401703200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140602T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140602T033000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Silicon Valley</title>
        <summary>Silicon Valley 1x08 "Optimal Tip-To-Top Efficiency"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/silicon-valley/season/1/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="308661401778800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140603T000000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140603T001100</dtend>
        <description>Finn and Jake learn about the food chain by becoming the food chain!</description>
        <title>Adventure Time</title>
        <summary>Adventure Time 6x06 "Food Chain"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/adventure-time/season/6/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199961401782400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140603T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140603T014500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x06 "Live Another Day: TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879181401876000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140604T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140604T040000</dtend>
        <description>Molly faces pressure to close the case, while Lester starts to feel like a new man.</description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x08 "The Heap"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="229231121401958800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140605T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140605T024500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x12 "We Are Grounders"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713171402047000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140606T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140606T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x07 " Fieldtrippers"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1395491402304400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140609T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140609T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x09 "The Watchers on the Wall"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028281402308000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140609T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140609T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x08</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199971402387200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140610T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140610T014500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x07 "Live Another Day: TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="26879191402480800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140611T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140611T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x09 "TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9617411402563600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140612T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140612T024500</dtend>
        <description>Mike and Harvey adjust to the new arrangement, butting heads over strategy; the firm learns that a disgraced former DA may be pursuing a vendetta.</description>
        <title>Suits</title>
        <summary>Suits 4x01 "One-Two-Three Go..."</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suits/season/4/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="229231131402563600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140612T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140612T024500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>The 100</title>
        <summary>The 100 1x13 "TBA - season finale"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-100/season/1/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713181402651800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140613T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140613T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x08 "A Little Respect"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="13954101402909200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140616T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140616T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Game of Thrones</title>
        <summary>Game of Thrones 4x10 "The Children"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/game-of-thrones/season/4/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23028291402912800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140616T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140616T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x09</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199981402992000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140617T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140617T014500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x08 "Live Another Day: TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="268791101403085600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140618T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140618T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Fargo</title>
        <summary>Fargo 1x10 "TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/fargo/season/1/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083311403085600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140618T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140618T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x01</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9617421403168400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140619T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140619T024500</dtend>
        <description>Harvey and Mike are on opposite sides of a takeover; Louis is partnered with a recent SEC defector in defending the firm.</description>
        <title>Suits</title>
        <summary>Suits 4x02 "Lunch and Dinner"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suits/season/4/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15977211403254800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140620T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140620T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Defiance</title>
        <summary>Defiance 2x01 "The Opposite of Hallelujah"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/defiance/season/2/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="23713191403256600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140620T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140620T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x09 "Nix the Fat Week"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="230282101403517600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140623T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140623T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x10</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="199991403596800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140624T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140624T014500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x09 "Live Another Day: TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083321403690400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140625T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140625T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x02</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="9617431403773200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140626T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140626T024500</dtend>
        <description>Logan Sanders pushes Harvey to prove his relationship with Mike will not hinder business; Louis tries to mend his relationship with his new colleague.</description>
        <title>Suits</title>
        <summary>Suits 4x03 "Two in the Knees"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/suits/season/4/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15977221403859600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140627T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140627T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Defiance</title>
        <summary>Defiance 2x02 "In My Secret Life"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/defiance/season/2/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="237131101403861400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140627T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140627T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x10 "Yearbook"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="11578311404115200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140630T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140630T020000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Unforgettable</title>
        <summary>Unforgettable 3x01 "New Hundred"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/unforgettable/season/3/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="230282111404122400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140630T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140630T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x11</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1999101404201600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140701T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140701T014500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x10 "Live Another Day: TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="19909211404208800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140701T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140701T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Under the Dome</title>
        <summary>Under the Dome 2x01 "Heads Will Roll"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/under-the-dome/season/2/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083331404295200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140702T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140702T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x03</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/3</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="237131111404466200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140704T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140704T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x11 "The Bottle"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="230282121404727200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140707T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140707T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x12</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1999111404806400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140708T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140708T014500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x11 "Live Another Day: TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/11</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083341404900000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140709T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140709T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x04</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/4</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="237131121405071000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140711T023000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140711T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Bad Teacher</title>
        <summary>Bad Teacher 1x12 "What's Old Is New"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/bad-teacher/season/1/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="230282131405332000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140714T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140714T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Devious Maids</title>
        <summary>Devious Maids 2x13</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/devious-maids/season/2/episode/13</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="1999121405411200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140715T010000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140715T014500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>24</title>
        <summary>24 9x12 "Live Another Day: TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/24/season/9/episode/12</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083351405504800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140716T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140716T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x05</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/5</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083361406109600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140723T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140723T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x06</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/6</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="308671406617200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140729T000000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140729T001100</dtend>
        <description>It's Princess Day in Ooo! You know what that means? Yep, LSP and Marceline team up to prank Breakfast Princess!</description>
        <title>Adventure Time</title>
        <summary>Adventure Time 6x07 "Princess Day"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/adventure-time/season/6/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083371406714400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140730T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140730T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x07</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/7</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083381407319200">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140806T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140806T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x08</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/8</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="15083391407924000">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140813T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140813T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x09</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/9</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="150833101408528800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20140820T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20140820T040000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Perception</title>
        <summary>Perception 3x10</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/perception/season/3/episode/10</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="10369411413190800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20141013T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20141013T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Homeland</title>
        <summary>Homeland 4x01 "TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/homeland/season/4/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="124511413190800">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20141013T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20141013T030000</dtend>
        <description>After learning that Terminus was nothing but a trap, Rick and the group must do whatever it takes to escape.</description>
        <title>The Walking Dead</title>
        <summary>The Walking Dead 5x01 "TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-walking-dead/season/5/episode/1</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="124521413795600">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20141020T020000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20141020T030000</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>The Walking Dead</title>
        <summary>The Walking Dead 5x02 "TBA"</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/the-walking-dead/season/5/episode/2</url>
    </event>
    <event uid="225511420196400">
        <dtstamp>20140510T234334Z</dtstamp>
        <dtstart>20150102T030000</dtstart>
        <dtend>20150102T034500</dtend>
        <description></description>
        <title>Heroes</title>
        <summary>Heroes 5x01</summary>
        <url>http://trakt.tv/show/heroes/season/5/episode/1</url>
    </event>
</calendar>
